and today is the twenty-sixth
I wanted to ask you a favor
but you know that there
fill the tank for me
please
truffle fabric and we'll put the strategy in gear
donut
the idea now is bro
does the management
control how sales are going here
here is selling well
does not remain
get the truffle of what is selling wrong
puts it where it's selling well
first expensive phase
is you test things you know
and there bro
softness
one more point
Trojan horse
we are closing by putting the trupas here
Valu Brunão
thank you
saw brother
oh i cleaned a chair too huh bro
anything says hello there Caião
how much do you pass on bro
a showcase
clean for them there
once a week
when you exchange value not price
that's what i say bro
things happen
another little farmer bro
you're so connected
O I cleaned this whole display case
remember me
I remember it's gone
because it might be 1 good chance for the 2 of us
give 1 hug here Guy
I'm here at Dona Couto and she gave a certain hand
also fall
need to make 1 showcase there Dude
deliver pamphlet
I do you this favor without charging anything
because you're putting me on truffles
bora bora
Alexandra
changed the concept here of her beauty salon
now she is dona coco
and need someone to deliver flyer
that's what i talk about
investment or return
my girl is on too
I'll see you what you're doing there
the cocoa show truffles now right
I said I didn't say
I can leave some here
rosemary
taca my cocoa show truffles
Trojan horse
gave good part
this guy here cleans showcase
say hello to me
has complete not to deliver
are you seeing
mano you can receive in cash or you pay with service
the choice is your face
unwinds
stop putting limitation there
the convenience
sells fast hand
tava lowering stock
so i just did the replacement here
I'm thinking here man
that i took the seat here from the chevas
but then I'm wondering if it would be worth me doing this
because I sleep in the car
if I ride something like that
it's 1 deal to use for a long time right
have these details to make investment
if you use little time
no longer use
come on here you had to do it there at the sawmill
how much do you find there
ah pay but some
500 account
ah oh
can put faith
caraca shelas
does not die
no guy
this о